

CONTACT

- 🔀 samolajide20@gmail.com
- +234 701 3890 879
- <u>£</u> Futa South Gate, Akure. Nigeria.
- https://cipherr.netlify.app

SKILLS

- Javascript
- TypeScript
- React / Redux / Next
- Node js
- Tailwind / MUI / Ant Design
- Solidity

SOFT SKILLS

Problem Solving, Collaboration, Empathy, Communication.

ACHIEVEMENTS

- KLAYTN HACKATON | Apr May 2022 Position: Second Place
- POLYGON HACKATON | May Jun 2022

Position: Second Place

• HARMONY HACKATON | Sep - Nov 2022 Covalent API prize.

PERSONAL PROJECTS

- https://weatherinfo-v2.netlify.app/
- https://redux-fakestore.netlify.app/

AFOLABI OLAJIDE SAMUEL

FRONT-END ENGINEER/ BLOCKCHAIN ENTHUSIAST.

I am a very passionate and dedicated web developer, who has had a passion for computing and programming since I was little. I am also very enthusiastic about blockchain technologies and I have worked on some projects that implement the technology.

EXPERIENCE

Senior Web Developer

Nufoundry NFT Project. | Oct 2020 - present

- Generated the NFT and metadata.
- Developed the smart contract
- Created the minting DApp.

Tech Stack: React, Solidity, Tailwind.

Front End Engineer

Languvi. | Dec 2022- present.

- Developed the website, from layout to function, according to client specifications
- Implemented special interface and experience to carry out transcription and translation.

Tech Stack: React, Tailwind, Redux.

Front End Engineer

Anya. | Dec 2022 - present.

- Worked with a team of engineers to develop views and logic.
- Improved some existing codes to proper standards.

Tech Stack: React, Redux, TypeScript, Ant Design.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Technology, Major in Computer Information Systems. GPA: 4.1

The Federal University Of Technology Akure | 2019 - 2024.

- Founder/President of Titans Hive Community.
- Member of the Campus Programming Club.